(Penny:)Your career is
far too important.
(Wyatt:)Behind every great man
is a nagging woman
(Wyatt:)who won't let him have any fun,
am I right, Leonard?
(Leonard:)Don't I know it.
(Wyatt:)Well, good night, son.
(Leonard:)Good night, Wyatt.
(Leonard:)Oh, good
night, honey.
(Wyatt:)Good night.
(Howard:)I love you.
(Penny:)Love you, too.
(Sheldon:)Oh, friggety-frak.
(Sheldon:)Not this again.
(Howard:)Three, four, five--
pass go, get 2,000 rupees--
(Howard:)six, seven.
(Howard:)Whoops. Can't go any further.
There's a sacred cow in my way.
(Raj:)Bernadette, please
tell your boyfriend
(Raj:)to cool it with
the cow jokes.
(Bernadette:)It won't help.
(Bernadette:)Once he finds a joke he likes,
he sticks with it.
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Raj:)Like his haircut material.